[Music]
Whenever someone suffers a loss in life, what do
people say? I know that many buffaloes go into the water, but
not in our village. What do they
say? Mummy says, it's
good that you took motor insurance in your pocket, otherwise you would have had to take a
loan. Guru, it's good that you
took health insurance, otherwise you would have had to mortgage your jewellery.
Then there was a flood and Ramesh said, it was good
that you took crop insurance, otherwise you would have had to
sell your land. Look brother, the buffalo will go into the water,
but not your savings.
Crores of people like him say the same thing, he did this and
took insurance.